Linh Dan!
Oh my god, run! Quick, run!
-Linh Dan!
-Open the door! Open the door!
Linh Dan!
Hey!
Thief! Thief!
Damn it!
-Are you alright?
-I'm fine, but my purse!
What are you looking at?
-My purse!
-Alright, wait a second!
Hey!
Sir, sir, my purse.
My purse, hey it's mine.
Stand up straight.
You bastard always
put hoes before bros!
Don't you ever feel bad?
I'd feel bad
if I have to dump girls for you.
Get it, bro?
So you and that girl?
As soon as she saw me,
she ordered a drink.
I could smell trouble!
Then? Tell me.
Of course I fled!
She's gorgeous
but I'm not into gold diggers.
I need training to play a yoga master
character in my new movie.
Is one month enough?
Don't worry, my yoga trainer
will turn you from
zero to hero before the shooting.
This is Uong Viet Hoang
the most famous Yoga PT in Saigon.
-And this…
-...is Uyen Thi.
I'm really into you.
I mean I'm really into your films.
Especially hot scenes.
Hmm, which film is that?
Any film she starred in is hot to me.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
This is Abu, my assistant.
You're the hottest in Saigon?
-Hoang, how many years of experience...
-Uh, Hoang has…
an international license in Samkhya Yoga,
Ashtanga Yoga, and Hatha Yoga.
Ask him anything you want.
Thank you.
I want whatever yoga
that gives me the tiny little waist
but gets my bust and hips…
larger.
There are three
qualities of a desirable man.
First, you gotta make the move.
A woman always
wants a man to take the reins.
Second, you need to be a man who can
give a woman every single thing she wants.
How about a mansion and a car?
Who told you that's what they want?
Women want to feel hopeful...
that if she's with you,
those things will be hers.
Sounds freaking deep.
Third, you have to make
a woman feel complete.
They always feel like
they're missing something
and need a man to provide their needs.
Sounds like taking care of an orphan?
Okay…
Let me pick up a girl.
Vietnamese keep their words!
Hello there.
It's my first time here.
Would you mind suggesting
me a good cocktail?
If it's alright,
you can order two glasses for us.
-Whichever one you favor the most.
-Thanks.
-But I don't drink with strangers.
-I don't either.
I don't know why but I
can't stop looking at you.
Maybe it's your hair…
your eyes… or your lips.
Or perhaps it's everything.
Seems like you don't
really enjoy this place.
What do you mean?
I'm the only one who's been drinking.
Don't tell me you're
trying to get me drunk.
What I mean is
I'm worried you might have to carry me
outta here. That doesn't seem right.
What if I've been trying to find an excuse
to carry you outta here?
Linh Dan!
Oh my god! Run, run!
Why didn't you tell me you had a husband?
I was going to tell you!
Oh my god!
He's going through
your wallet… He's looking at your ID!
You might have to go abroad for a while.
He knows where you live!
-Leave the country?
-Oh my god…
...he's got a knife and
threatened to kill me! What now?
Listen, you need to stay calm.
Breathe deep and exhale slowly.
First thing you gotta do…
run out the house…
and call the cops immediately, okay?
Or should I give him the phone
and you apologize to him?
-Is that okay?
-I need to hide!
I thought you'd be too old to be fooled!
It was my dad this morning.
Why would I be married?
Jeez…
-It's not fun, alright!
-It's so funny.
I'm dying laughing
but you don't think it's funny?
Anyway, come over to
get your wallet and phone back.
My dad's not home.
He went to buy a security camera.
What if he suddenly comes home?
Well, you run faster than him!
Plus, I am the one who should be scared.
Is your big sister home?
What sister? It's me.
Were you so drunk last night
that you don't even remember me?
Anyway, come inside.
Come in!
We just met, okay?
And right now,
I don't want to have a girlfriend.
Also, from looking at
your appearance and age
we're clearly not a good match.
I don't want you to misunderstand.
But last night we slept together.
You're not the type of jerk
that tricks girls to sleep with you
then never see them again, right?
That's enough.
Before you leave,
-I have something to show you.
-How about next time?
Do you want your stuff back or not?
Ready?
It's really nice. Take a look.
Let go of me!
Don't, please don't! Don't do it!
Don't!
Let go!
Oh man...
I'm not going to show you the end.
So embarrassing!
Plus, you're as fierce as a tiger!
Why did you record that?
Because it's my first time,
so I wanted a keepsake.
Your first time?
I'm still in school.
Here. Look at this.
D.O.B 31/05/1999
-You're not yet...
-...not yet what?
-You're not 18 yet?
-Mmhm!
-Wow.
-But babe.
Don't worry. If I don't tell the
cops then they won't arrest you, right?
I know how to keep a secret.
I know you want to remember
the milestones in your life.
But some milestones
shouldn't be recorded...
Just keep them in our memories.
That way it will be..
more meaningful.
Then let's delete it.
Yeah.
But it was my first time.
And our first memory together as well.
How could I erase that?
Are you freaking kidding me?
Are you nuts?
Nuts? What do you mean?
What do you want?
Just tell me what I need
to do so you'll erase that clip.
I want to be your girlfriend.
But actually I've been
your girlfriend since last night.
Between us there is no
"boyfriend girlfriend" business.
And today
will be the last time we're
going to see each other. OK?
Are we clear?
Stop! If the cops
...looked at this footage
...would they think I was willing?
Three o'clock tomorrow afternoon,
pick me up from school.
Now get home safe, alright?
WELLSPRING INTERNATIONAL BILINGUAL SCHOOL
SIX DAYS EARLIER...
We just got a venue sponsor, Gala Center!
And here,
are the expected stage designs this year.
Tick-tock, tick-tock!
Hurry up to find yourself a prom date!
And lastly but most importantly,
this year's prom theme is... REUNION!
Tony!
How dare you do this to me?
This isn't me.
How dare you say it's not you?
I didn't post it, didn't know anything.
Linh Dan!
I only kissed her once.
Just one kiss huh?
Yeah, just one kiss.
Poor Linh Dan...
Looks like this year's prom it's my
destiny to be the Queen next to King Tony!
I'd better start taking dance lessons!
Keep dreaming, I'm gonna be the King!
What? You're the prom King?
-Wake up, sis.
-I'm gonna hit you in the face with this!
Some people are not even the stars
but trying too hard to outshine the Sun...
-Now do you guys believe me?
-About what?
About Tony, what else?
-Tony will be mine.
-Mmhm!
-And I'm going to be the Queen this year.
-Yes!
Darling aren't you
at the library to study?
KIET: OMG YEN STOLE LINH DAN'S BOYFRIEND?
VU: NO BOY CAN RESIST YEN.
MY: I GUESS YEN SHALL
BE THIS YEAR'S QUEEN.
TRANG: IT SERVES HER RIGHT, NOT
BEING ABLE TO KEEP SUCH A HOT BOYFRIEND.
I need to be her friend.
What's bothering you, "sis"?
Must be that dog Tony, isn't it ?
He pissed you off "sis"?
Just say a word and I'll mess him up!
Are you possessed, Dad?
Hey no need to call me "dad" now.
Just see me as a friend!
So it's easier to talk, to be close.
-Let's teach that dog Tony a lesson!
-Dad!
I'm begging you, stop talking like that!
Yeah, I get it.
Dad...
Please never mention
Tony in front of me again.
Where did you buy this?
Guys, yesterday Tony
told me my hair looked pretty.
Really?
Do you guys know any
eye drops that reduce swelling?
I do. But are your eyes swollen?
Nah. It's for someone else.
Linh Dan.
Are you still angry?
What'd you do if it was you?
But you're wrong to
make a big deal out of it this time.
Tony's the one who made a big deal.
Well there's a party coming up...
and the prom at the end of the year.
-We planned everything already.
-I don't care.
If this goes on, how can we follow you?
This room has lots of light bulbs so...
won't need another one to outshine, OK?
You should stay away from me before people
see us together and make you embarrassed.
Come on, let me apologize.
You know you've
always been my only friend.
But as soon as you were in love
with Tony, you ignored me.
Because every time I took
you along, people kept teasing you.
So you pitied me?
Not hanging out with me
made you feel less guilty right?
Forget it...
I mean, what's so great about Tony?
He's just tall,
handsome, and plays basketball well.
That's all.
-But...
-He's gonna feel bad soon...
for losing someone like you.
You need to find a mature man.
Firstly, he can lead you.
Secondly, he can provide for you.
And finally, he must complete you.
UONG VIET HOANG, 35 YEARS OLD
HEIGHT 174 CM
IF ONE'S LIFE IS LIKE
SPRING, SUMMER, FALL, WINTER.
THEN THIS GUY'S SPRING...
...SEEMS ENDLESS.
BUT TODAY,
IT WILL...
END!
I didn't want things to be like that.
You're really scaring me.
But is he handsome?
Of course!
And is he polite and a gentleman?
Huh, he doesn't need
to be a polite gentleman.
You devil! When do I get to meet him?
He should be here by now.
Hoang, there's nothing to be ashamed of.
You are just a normal guy.
Maybe a little older, that's all.
Picking up a student from
school is normal. Just think of it as...
Uncle, you can't park here.
Bye Uncle.
Shit, how could I be so careless!
Hoang! Do you like kids?
I really hate kids. I despise them!
My wife is pregnant.
I just wanted to share the news.
Can you turn to the right a bit?
PT Uong Viet Hoang, please...
come to the meeting room now. Thank you.
Hoang, rule number
three in the Employee Handbook?
Yes sir.
The third rule
in the Employee Code of Conduct...
is...
-No fraternizing with clients.
-Yes.
But I regret to say that I have been told
that one person among you guys
has violated the rule.
You must all know who that person is.
I'm sorry but we have to let you go.
Duy!
Pack your things. You're fired!
-It's okay, it's okay.
-Why crying, Hoang?
Such a pity, Duy.
Hoang get over here right now!
You get out quickly or I'm coming in!
I can see your white hair,
don't try to hide!
Your sis is looking for you.
Must be family emergency. Excuse me.
His mom popping out another kid?
She was born in
the year of the Pig, you know...
Linh Dan is that you?
You think you can get rid of me?
I dare you to leave me!
Bye Hoang.
-Hi there.
-See you tomorrow, eh?
My little sister.
When will Tuan finish his shift?
I don't know.
You think I won't
spank you, little sister? Quiet!
Quiet! You are too much.
-Why are you here?
-Why did you hide from me?
Adults must work. Get it?
I don't care. I want you
to be serious with me. OK?
This is where I work.
And you are not
allowed to come here. You hear me?
Why not?
Because adults really need to work
and are very afraid to lose their jobs.
Get it?
Oh, maybe I should meet
your boss and talk to him directly!
-That's enough.
-Now what're you going to do?
I will be serious with you. Fine?
-What else?
-Here's your "boyfriend schedule".
Really, there's a schedule?
Don't worry,
I've avoided your work schedule
and the rest of your time, is mine!
By the way, honey, my friends
told me there's a good rom-com out.
Let's go. Pick me up at seven OK? Bye!
-I'm leaving now, Dad.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait. Sweetie.
Where did you meet this guy?
Why is he hiding from me?
You're watching him like that,
who wouldn't be scared?
-Hey...
-Bye, Dad.
Hey, hey, listen to me first.
Look, you must always be
careful of those grabby guys.
Maybe your daughter
is the one with the grabby hands.
Don't be crude.
Show me some self defense moves.
-Let me see them!
-Cut it out, Dad...
Hey, wanna go out or not?
Are you hurt?
Lucky for me you were gentle. But for
those other guys, triple the power!
Get in!
What are you doing?
You never saw a girl do martial arts?
It doesn't look that cruel.
-One ticket for "Fast and Furious" please.
-Yes.
-One ticket?
-Thank you.
I'll go in first.
What kind of boyfriend is that?
What do you mean? I didn't
know which film you wanted to watch.
You've gone too far!
OK, if you don't like it, break up.
No one makes you suffer.
You've never gone to
the movies with anyone?
A waste of money and time.
How about I take you home and we do "it"?
Doesn't that sound more fun?
How can you treat
someone you love like that?
-Why the hell would I love anyone?
-You're disgusting!
I do what I like.
No one can change that!
Linh Dan!
Hi!
-Hello!
-Hey, who're you going to the movies with?
Ah, this is Hoang, my new boyfriend.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
Oh, hi guys... Ah, hi boss.
Yeah yeah sure, if you
think it's okay then I'm okay!
-Who's he talking to?
-But are you okay with it, boss?
Yep.
Hey, what, what're you doing? Let go!
If you're my boyfriend,
I want you to be one for real.
I am very real. Otherwise,
I would have stayed home.
I want you to look at me
like the first time you met me.
I didn't know you were underage then.
-Do I look underage to you?
-That's enough.
-Are these legs of an underage girl?
-Drop it.
Feel anything?
Please let go. Oh shit, what the...
Let go!
There are people around and cameras!
Are you crazy? Let me go.
No touching or anything, no kissing...
No hugging or cuddling... You hear me?
You were so passionate
but now can't get it up?
Can't get it up my ass!
Don't talk to me, be quiet!
113, what is your emergency?
I'm sorry, I dialed
the wrong number. I meant to dial 114.
If you don't want
to go to jail, then don't mess with me.
Starting tomorrow
you must follow my rules.
One, add me on Facebook.
Change status to "in a relationship."
Two, no honking in front of my house.
Get off and open the door for me.
Three, take me to and pick
me up from school on time, OK?
Shut your jaw.
What, she's 17?
You're braver than me.
I swear to you, Dad,
she looked like 18 or 19 years old.
Say those nonsense to the jury in court.
Even if she said she was 20, I bet
you would believe her if you saw her.
The law doesn't care how she looks, only
look at her legal documents. Come on, son.
I swear to you next time I'm
gonna check the ID of every single girl!
Is there a next time?
you're going to jail for life.
You need to rescue your son!
How can I help you? I'm a lawyer,
-not some gangster to break the law.
-How can you say that?
I have a suggestion.
Hire some gangsters to steal her phone
and then erase that video clip.
Ten lawyers like me couldn't help!
You're the best lawyer.
How come I didn't think of that!
If you knew how to
think with your real head
then things wouldn't be this way.
Quick, open the door for me.
I'm late for class.
Oh shit!
-What?
-Where is it?
Where did I put it? Where's my phone?
Man, I'm screwed.
-What?
-I can't find my phone.
Can you call me?
I'm late already!
Linh Dan!
-Are you seeing another guy?
-Oh, am I?
Who is that guy?
Why care about that guy?
He's got nothing to do with you.
-You don't think I can find out who he is?
-Then do it.
Ah, don't bother wasting
money on buying me flowers.
Waste my time throwing them away!
-Oh my god. Disaster!
What a joke telling
me to run for prom King!
Me too. Have you ever seen a man
wearing a dress and then become Queen?
Down with the Organizing Committee!
-Strike!
-Strike! Down with the Organizing Board!
-Against what?
-Just follow me!
-Uh, strike!
-Down with the Organizing Committee!
-Why are you making such a big deal?
They put you guys in the running
in order not to be
accused of discrimination.
Oh my gosh.
Shut up bitch,
pissed 'cause you're jealous?
Linh, Linh, Linh, Linh!
Come here. Quickly.
Not "Linh"! It's "Lynne."
Ok Lynne, whatever. Quick, come here.
How about we become a couple?
Let me finish!
You need to man up to
become the prom King.
And I need to be girly
and feminine to become the Queen.
Then once we win,
we'll switch crowns. Get it?
Good, good, good!
How is this possible? Oh my god!
My parents came home early
all of a sudden. I can't help it.
We had no problem the whole year.
But the year end house party is ruined.
What's going on?
What do we do now?
Can we find another place?
-Your house?
-My house is nice but really small.
-But my boyfriend's there every night.
Your house? How about yours?
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Hi honey!
Today I want to cook you dinner
to celebrate our first night together.
It's only been a few days,
what's to celebrate?
Every night is a celebration of our love.
-What are you doing?
-Ah, nothing at all.
Hi! What's his name? He's so cute!
-Meow.
-You named a dog "Meow"?
I like it. Hey Meow, don't touch her.
She's not 18 yet.
Lick and you'll
regret it for the rest of your life.
You just called yourself a dog, you know.
Nothing to do huh? Come here and help me.
Do you like to eat spaghetti?
Now, do you want me to...
-Hey!
-Me first.
I need to take Meow out to pee.
'Cause if I don't,
he'll pee all over the house.
He looks innocent,
but he's very dangerous.
Hang up please, come on!
Hey what's taking you so long? Hurry up!
Here's yours.
-Eat up!
-It smells so good!
-Looks yummy. Bon appétit!
-After you.
Is it good?
I've never had spaghetti so delicious.
Easy with the compliments.
Maybe it's also
because I'm so happy right now.
Well, your girlfriend cooked for you,
of course you're happy!
It's not that. Because...
I have some news that is both
good and bad and I want to tell you.
Good for me and bad for you...
I'll go home to study after dinner.
While you stay and wash dishes.
Then we'll see who's sad, OK?
Ignore the dishes for now,
I just deleted the video.
Honey.
I already saved it online.
It doesn't matter if
you removed it from my phone.
This news is truly happy and sad...
But I'm the happy one,
and you're the sad one.
Eat up honey!
Remember to pick me up on time tomorrow.
Tomorrow's Saturday, you're off school,
why should I pick you up?
Because I want us to
take Meow out for a walk.
-What for?
-So that he knows
that there is a new member in his family.
Bear, look! That's my little Meow.
I think you two should switch names.
What are you cooking tonight?
Many things, but I'm not cooking.
Just to let you know I can't cook.
What's going on?
Linh Dan! Why you're just coming?
You're late.
Come on! Quick quick quick quick!
How could they get in my house?
When you swiped my phone before...
I swiped your house keys.
What the hell is this?
-What's going on here?
-What do you mean?
-You've never thrown a house party?
-That's none of your business, OK?
I'm calling the cops.
Babe, are you really going to call them?
Why didn't you do it at
your own house but mine, huh?
Because I wanted to.
What are you going to do about it?
-Thanks girl!
-It's my new boyfriend's house.
-Mmhm!
-What?
Your boyfriend's house is pretty roomy!
Mmhm, of course. He's got a car,
his own place, and a good job.
Unlike some immature boys.
Hey! What are you guys doing?
Calm down, calm down.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
No cigarettes, OK?
Who said they're cigarettes, bro?
Go home.
-Hoang!
-Tony?
Long time no see, bro!
Where are you going?
This is my house.
Oh, you know Tony?
Tony is my cousin.
What an interesting coincidence!
I didn't know you knew Linh Dan.
This is my new boyfriend.
Stop lying.
You don't know my cousin.
He'd rather die than have a girlfriend.
Babe, tell your innocent cousin the truth.
She's my girlfriend.
Well, looks like my cousin is very fond
of using second-hand stuff from me...
This surprises me a bit.
Keep dreaming. You and I never did it!
Excuse me,
I need to talk to Linh Dan alone.
Next time don't forget
to tell your family about me.
Aw shit.
This is...
-Freaking bad.
-Get it?
-Got it.
Break it down.
First those two guys took
a chair and broke it on Hoang.
Then he went there,
heard something shattered,
saw three guys pulling one's pants down.
Then Hoang went over there to kick
out those guys smoking non-cigarettes.
That was when he saw Tony and Yen.
Finally, Hoang took Linh Dan
outside while Tony stayed with Yen.
You set all this up.
-I'm scared of you.
-I have my own reasons.
What's that got to do with me? Huh?
Does it seem fair?
You also only care about yourself,
and nobody else. Don't talk "fair" to me!
But you're the one
who trapped me that night.
Don't tell me you didn't like it.
I'm not doing this anymore.
If you think that I can make
Tony feel hurt, then just take a look.
Does he look hurt?
Here's my iCloud.
If you wanna erase it, go ahead.
It's boring here.
Let's go to the after-party!
Done crying?
From tomorrow, we have
nothing to do with each other.
I'll take you home.
Don't bother.
Join us.
Why you play so bad today?
-That girl's bothering you?
-That's enough.
I need to find a way to
help her forget Tony.
I didn't think you would be here.
Maybe it's because
old habits die hard.
Maybe it'll last
until the end of this month.
Hi, please support us.
You've been sad long enough.
Now get up and fight!
Fight? Fight with whom? What would I get?
Are you kidding?
You need to be the
Queen 'cause you deserve it.
They cannot be King and Queen.
If that happens this school is ruined!
But think about it.
Yen's not just pretty but about to
compete in the cheerleader championship
and is dating Tony. I have nothing.
I knew you would say that!
Let's look at the SWOT chart, OK?
First you need to utilize your strengths,
which is...
the highest GPA in school.
Then come up with something that
goes well with our prom theme "Reunion".
I don't even have a prom date...
Hoang is only with me
until the end of the month.
You're just going to accept his deadline?
Why you so honest?
The annual badminton championship
registration is open starting tomorrow.
Why're you here?
Aren't you embarrassed?
You haven't gotten her yet
so you keep hanging around, right?
Linh Dan needs a real man to be with,
not a boy trying hard to be a man.
Hey I don't know any of this.
Neither do I. I'm a yoga instructor.
But you don't need martial arts
to know how to punch.
What important is,
in order to build something new,
you must break the old.
Now I'll count from one to three,
and you smash his face for me.
Yeah. One...
Are you hurt?
OK, I got it,
now get up and we'll do it again.
I don't dare do it again.
-Did you see it?
-I'm not blind!
That's a lot of money.
Where did you get it?
From your wallet.
It's for charity.
Hello, this is Hung.
Hello sir.
-Is Linh Dan home, sir?
-Yes, what do you want?
I'm here.
Please tell Linh Dan to go outside please.
If you're here, come in, not "go out"!
Oh never mind, sir.
Something just came up.
I need to go home right away,
please tell her I'm sorry.
Okay. I'll tell her.
How tricky you are!
Look at this!
Wow! We gotta celebrate big!
-OK, but you're buying, son.
-OK!
-Why you're only eating mangoes?
-I'm craving sour.
-What is it?
-We're busted.
Wait for me.
-How?
He's looking at us.
-At you or me?
-How can I know?
Then we haven't been spotted!
But what's the difference
between seeing me or you?
Well we're not twins
so of course it's different.
I'm so worried.
You haven't been spotted.
See? I told you we haven't been spotted.
You're right. Yeah!
Hey, I'm not doing this anymore.
-Why?
-They saw us already.
No they haven't. Look at his face!
That's right. You haven't been spotted.
Your camera is pretty clear.
That's my camera.
Hi sweetheart.
Actually it's my first time here.
You think you
could suggest a delicious cocktail for me?
Or perhaps you can order
for both of us your favorite cocktail?
Oh, thank you.
But I don't drink with strangers.
Truth is, me neither,
but from the moment I saw you
there's something about
you that made me keep looking at you.
Is it your white hair?
Or your small eyes?
I used to hate playboys like you.
But now it's different.
Different in what way?
When you love someone, you
give them the ability to hurt you.
You have figured out a truth of life.
Love is the biggest mistake of humanity.
-Exactly, baby.
-Cheers!
I swear I'll never ever date
another boy again!
Me too! If I ever love
some bimbo, I'll call myself a dog!
Down with love!
-Down with love!
-Down with bimbos!
-Hello
-Hello, this is Tony, sir.
Tony! You're an asshole!
I'm Hung, Linh Dan's father.
I'm looking for my daughter.
Um, my name is Hoang.
She isn't here.
Can I come inside for a drink?
My house is out of water.
-Well, beer is okay.
-Uh, you came here too suddenly.
I didn't have time to prepare anything.
Perhaps we can meet tomorrow?
-Then I'll just come in for a bit.
-But my dog may bite...
Lately he's been putting
a lot of people in the hospital.
He's more dangerous than he looks.
-What's his name?
-Meow.
Meow!
Move! So I can talk to the dog.
Meow! Ha! Ha!
Coast is clear.
Ah...
You said you ran out of drinks?
Well you wanted beer. This is liquor.
Have a drink, sir.
Uhm, we're nearly the same age.
Call me "bro", it feels more friendly.
-No sir, I don't dare.
-Dating a girl under 18,
what else you wouldn't dare do?
Uhm... sir...
Sir, listen to me. The truth is,
Linh Dan and I are just normal friends.
-Ha! "Normal?"
-Yes.
You just need 30 seconds for it
to become abnormal.
Yes, well... Sir!
-You're such a joker, sir!
-Again with the "sir"!
Sorry bro.
That's enough. I'm leaving.
So your place is really out of beer?
You're still up?
I have lots to read for my test tomorrow.
You have a test tomorrow but
still went out with him all day?
Dad, you know he has a name.
Everyone has a name.
Even thieves have names.
He didn't steal anything from you,
why are you acting like that?
-Why shouldn't I be?
-But dad, nothing is going on at all.
I'm just dating Hoang for fun, that's all.
-Oh my god!
-"Dating for fun"?
Your idea of fun is killing me.
But you have to trust me.
Of course I trust you.
But that white haired punk?
That's a face you cannot trust.
But you told me to never judge a
person by their appearance.
But you're not allowed to
explore what's inside him either.
-What are you saying? Gross!
-OK, let's do this.
-This weekend, tell him to come see me.
-Why?
If he's a good guy, meet me!
Hoang, among my personal trainers
you're the most gentlemanly of all.
When we're training,
I feel so comfortable with you.
Even if I was totally nude right now,
I'd still feel perfectly safe.
If you were to do that,
then it'd be very dangerous.
Where's your phone?
This weekend,
nine p.m., holiday date with a superstar.
Ooh, I'm in top three everyone!
Don't make me slap your face!
What kinda king reacts like that?
The principal
would like to remind all seniors
to focus on final exams
even though prom is coming up.
Today is my last day with Hoang already.
So what's your plan for this holiday?
Not yet.
I'll stay home and study.
I've been going out so much I haven't
touched my books. I'm pretty worried.
Do you want to have a
drink before I take you home?
Nah, it's the last time
you're picking me up anyway.
Alright then.
Guess I'll get going now.
Study hard.
Hoang! I'm late...
Late?
I'm three weeks late...
Does anyone else know?
VU ANH INTERNATIONAL GENERAL HOSPITAL
Let go of me!
It's only been three weeks. Follow me!
How can you say that? It's our child!
Are you crazy?
How can you go to school while pregnant?
Come on!
If you're too scared, just say so!
-Linh Dan!
-Yes I'm a student...
but I'm not going to get an abortion!
Oh, hi boss. That girl must've
been talking to someone else.
I'm talking to you, who else?
Don't ever force me to get an abortion!
Stay away from my wife!
Quy, please.
You need to let me explain, Quy.
Quy! Quy, Quy!
She's my niece's age
but you couldn't leave her be?
Quy!
I've looked the other way many times.
-But not this time.
-But Quy...
Pack your things. You're fired.
You're killing me, Quy. Quy!
This weekend, nine p.m.,
holiday date with a superstar.
I'm listening.
I've been calling you,
why you didn't pick up?
Pick up for what?
I just got fired. Are you happy now?
Why are you so rude?
I didn't know you got fired.
Whose fault is that?
-You think it's mine?
-Forget it.
-My dad wants to see you.
-What?
Exact seven tonight at my house, OK?
No way. I have a date tonight.
Don't worry, I haven't told my dad yet.
But if you don't show up,
then there's going to be trouble.
Bye bye.
Uyen Thi!
-Oh... hello...
-The dog!
Hoang's dog! It choked on a fish bone.
So he had to bring
him to the vet immediately.
So he asked me to
come here to keep you company.
Babe!
What the...
Do I look younger to you?
You look like you just
got out of the mental hospital.
You couldn't just be yourself?
How can I be myself?
I can't be myself around your dad!
Well, whatever you're
trying to do isn't working.
What's not working?
Do you know how much this costs?
Why didn't you shave?
Oh crap, I forgot to shave.
-Hoang!
-What?
My Gramma and relatives are inside.
You don't have time to shave.
-Now I have more reason to shave.
-No way, you're already late.
This is Hoang, my boyfriend.
He's teaching me yoga.
Ah yes. Hello family.
You have a lovely house, sir.
It's so comfortable, and I really
love when a house has a yard like this.
I designed this yard to do yoga, you know.
-Now that Linh Dan isn't here...
-Yes?
Let's call each other "bro" okay?
To make things easier.
Don't say that bro,
because if you're my bro,
then how do I address your daughter?
Good one.
You are really good. You're old,
but how can you
confide in and talk to her so well?
What's your secret? Show me.
Dad, are you finished threatening him?
Can I have him back now?
Hey I'm not threatening anyone.
We're just talking.
-You guys stay here and talk, okay?
-Goodnight Dad.
Hey, when are you
going to ask me to the prom?
If someone else invites me, don't cry, OK?
Who told you I want to go to the prom?
It's my senior year's prom.
You know how important it is to me.
Oh god, now it's prom,
prom, prom, prom, prom?
Hey, are you going to go?
I'm telling my dad.
What so... random.
What's this got to do with your dad?
I'll tell my dad
you made me get an abortion.
Dad!
God, I feel like I'm way too evil.
He's been evil to many people!
What goes around comes around.
But it's a fake pregnancy.
He's not having to take care of any baby.
Hey... hey!
Don't tell me you're in love him!
No, I'm not in love with anyone.
Right now is not the time to waver.
Don't forget your plan to make Hoang
take you to the prom, become Queen
and dance with him in front of
everyone when Tony becomes King
so Tony can feel the
pain that he caused you.
One, two, three! Alright, got it.
-This is good, right?
-It's a bit small. A little bigger please.
There you go!
-More!
-More?
That's it.
Perfect. Thank you!
Hey. Let's go.
WILL THE BASKETBALL TEAM AND CHEERLEADERS
BECOME IN-LAWS AFTER THEIR ROYAL VICTORY?
This girl is too much. We
gotta make sure your clip is way better.
-Does it make sense here?
-Mmhm.
No ma'am, I am a yoga
instructor, not a masseur.
Uh, no, I don't do that kind of massage.
Don't worry, I won't let you starve.
MY SON
-What's going on, Hoang?
-I have something to ask.
When you had me,
... were you and Mom married yet?
Where is this coming from?
Of course not!
Then when you knew Mom was pregnant,
-... did you take her to get an abortion?
-What?
Why are you bringing up the past?
Of course I did.
Wait if you did, then why am I still here?
Because you were too stubborn.
She drank the strongest, blackest
medicines, but you wouldn't let go.
You were that cruel?
I'm just teasing you.
I proposed to your mom right away.
-Were you scared?
-Of course I was!
But now when I look back on it,
I was more happy than scared.
-What were you happy about?
-Well, because of you
I was able to marry your mother.
But why are you
asking me about all of this?
Is it about the 17-year-old girl?
Uh, no.
I didn't call today to ask for help, Dad.
I just wanted to tell you some news.
You're about to have a grandchild.
And I really love Linh Dan.
Dad? Dad?
I wish your mother was still here
so she could hear what you just said.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
What are you doing? Don't try
to trick me into doing anything bad!
Oh please, only you'd try to trick a guy,
not the other way around!
-Ready?
-Yup!
Slowly, ok?
I have a new job.
And I will start next week.
-Hoang...
-I know, I know...
Let's not say anything for now.
Because right now,
anything we say will
come out super cheesy.
I know I am the first man in your life.
But I want you...
...to be the last hot girl in my life.
Will you marry me?
Oh, I know, I know, I know.
You probably knew it right away, right?
The lady who sold it to me said that
if you're not in the business,
there's no way you could
tell this diamond's fake!
I promise you that
when I have enough money,
I'll exchange this fake
rock with a real one for you.
I'm sorry.
Babe, I should be the one who says sorry.
I've been trying to find a
way to tell you but I couldn't.
The truth is,
I'm not pregnant.
I said that because I wanted you
to take me to the prom.
And that night...
nothing happened between the two of us.
What did you say?
I'm sorry, Hoang.
I just want to ask you one question.
From the moment that
we knew each other until now,
was anything real?
Well, that's great then.
I'm here, Dad.
So, how's the prep
going for my grandchild?
-Yeah.
-Remember to get a crib,
-so he can sleep separately, OK?
-Yes.
Get him a mattress, bed sheets, blankets,
oh but remember the
sheets should be moisture proof.
Get some toys and stuff to
dangle above the crib so it's more lively.
The most important thing is to
get rid of all sharp things in the house,
or just cover them up.
Especially electric sockets.
Cover it or place stuff up high.
Ah, also pregnant women
tend to be very cranky and difficult.
Take it easy on her,
massage her, love her and
don't fight with her, understand?
If you fight and make her sad,
she might give birth to an ugly baby!
Man, what's wrong with you?
You look horrible.
Prom's coming you know.
I don't care about the prom anymore.
But what's wrong?
Linh Dan!
Phuong...
Phuong, will you be my prom date?
There must be some kind
of force leading you closer and closer,
until you see me standing in front of you,
...swaggering, and dashing.
What do you think? You like it?
Me wearing this dress in a pink limo to
the prom tonight would be killer!
What's wrong with you?
What're you staring at?
Are you even listening to me?
What's now? Babe.
Hello?
What's up? Say it quickly!
Are you busy? In a rush?
Not really, but do you need anything?
No.
What's wrong, Hoang?
Well I was just going to ask
if you wanted to go out tonight.
I'm busy tonight.
-You have a date?
-Going to the movie.
You have a girlfriend?
-Who is it?
-Don't be nosy!
What a mood killer!
-Uyen Thi!
-I'm here to visit your "Meow".
Is he better?
Oh thanks, he's much better.
Why did you feed him fish bones?
I bought some dog food for him.
Aw, look at him!
Do you know that because of you,
he left me waiting all night?
This is the first time
ever that I was made a fool.
And yet someone hasn't even apologized.
Have a drink and let me apologize.
I forgive you.
On the condition that
...you won't forgive me.
Meow is looking at you.
Would you rather he look at you?
Hey it's sweet and sour soup!
Not with fish but shrimp! It's delicious.
Eat up! Mmm, here you go.
Here's a fresh cauliflower.
Very fresh, eat up, darling.
-Dad.
-Huh?
I told you I'm fine.
Stop worrying about me.
Ah, I'm not even worried. Just eat up.
I'm going to bite your ear, OK?
I'm sorry.
-I can't do this.
-What?
You can't do this with me?
Superstar Uyen Thi?
Whoever you are, it doesn't matter.
Hey...
...we locked the dog outside?
I have something urgent to take care of.
When I get a chance,
I'll tell you the story,
and you will understand. Alright?
Huh?
Can I get a round of
applause for our 2017 prom?
-Hello?
-Hello, Mister Hung? It's Hoang.
Now don't say anything bro.
Let me do the talking.
If you truly want to be
friend with Linh Dan, help her,
connect with her,
you need to get her to the
prom by any means necessary.
Will you?
Right now all other kids have left
their parents at home to go to the prom.
Only my daughter is at home with her dad.
Those who went to the prom all have dates.
But I swore I would
never love anyone anymore.
So I stay home, not
because I'm being obedient or something.
I like you this way!
I like you coldhearted.
I don't want you to love anyone either.
Whenever you're in
love it's exhausting for me.
Hey, but there's one thing,
you need to go to the prom.
Weddings can happen a few times,
but prom is once in a lifetime.
But who goes to the prom alone,
Dad? I'd die of embarrassment.
Your English sucks.
Stick to Vietnamese, Dad.
Shine your light ! Shine Your
Light! Shine Your Light! Shine Your Light!
Linh Dan!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I thought you were
sad so I didn't want to tell you.
-But which jerk are you coming with?
-This jerk.
-I'm sorry sir.
-And who are you with?
He's practicing so later
we can dance together.
Our last nominee for Queen has arrived.
Linh Dan, please come onstage.
It's your turn. Get up there.
-Nah...
-I've already prepared everything.
It doesn't matter to me anymore.
But you're not
doing this just for yourself.
Did you already forget our goal?
Get on the stage.
Go, go!
What are you waiting for? Get up there!
It feels like just yesterday
we were asking each
others' names at the schoolyard.
But in the blink of an eye,
three years have flown by.
My father said that in your lifetime,
you may have a few weddings,
but prom is once in a lifetime.
So I had to come here tonight with my Dad.
It's possible that after tonight,
we might not remember each others' names,
or maybe we won't even
remember each others' faces.
But we will never
forget our title, Class of 2017!
Thank you all for making me wiser,
cry less, and laugh more.
Thank you Phuong.
And finally I want to thank you Dad,
you really are my best friend.
Why are you here when you
said you didn't want to go to the prom?
Um... I wanted to see you for a second...
Hey you!
Why you told me to bring her here
if you're just going to talk for a second?
Ah...
You were the one who called.
Dad... Why don't you let him talk?
As for you, you're here now. Now what?
Linh Dan...
I...
This is for making
me go to the prom alone.
And this is for kicking me out.
And this one's for not saying anything.
So say something!
He's speechless.
Do something.
I love you!
Who's 'you'?
Linh Dan.
I love you.
But I'm 20 years younger than you.
I will love you until the day I die.
I'm still a little girl you know.
Then that's even better.
Um, I will love you forever.
"Whoever falls in love again, is a dog."
Are you sure? Hmm?
Woof!
-Hey Vu.
-Yeah?
-Have you ever kissed anyone?
-Not yet.
-Then what's it like to be kissed?
-I'd like to know too.
And now for the
moment everyone has been waiting for.
We have the result for our 2017 King,
the person who has brought
honor to our school. And that person is
...Tony!
Please can we have the 2016 King and Queen
to come onstage to pass on their crowns.
Thuc Linh Lincoln will
now crown our 2017 King.
And now who will be our 2017 Queen?
We now have the result.
Is our Queen someone who's
beautiful and a great dancer?
Or beautiful and a top student?
Now, no more wondering,
the 2017 Prom Queen is
... Linh Dan!
And now Ky Nguyen will
give the crown to our Queen tonight!
And again thank you to
2016 King and Queen.
And now our new King and
Queen will start the first dance tonight.
What I first wanted to do...
was to leave you here.
And have Hoang to dance with me instead.
So you'd be embarrassed.
So you'd know
what it feels to be left in the dust.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
I think... there's only
one guy deserves to be with you tonight.
Know what? I'm 18 now.
Honey, do you
think Uyen Thi is a little...
too "young" for this role?
-Here you go.
-What?
This week I've bought you three
popcorn and two sodas, you know.